{"Question":"Solve Compound Inequalities : -1 < x + 3 < 5","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":3,"Answer":"-4 < x < 2","Source":"Beginning Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[x + 3 + 1 >0, x + 3 - 5 < 0, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Solve Compound Inequalities : 3x < 18 and 5x > -20","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":3,"Answer":"-4 < x < 6","Source":"Beginning Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[3*x - 18 < 0, 5*x + 20 > 0, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"-5<= 2x -1 <= 7","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":3,"Answer":null,"Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[2*x-1+5 >=0, 2*x-1 -7 <=0 ,x , solve]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"A fitness enthusiast wants to maintain his weight and has determined that he needs to burn at least 2000 but no more than 2500 calories per day through a combination of diet and exercise. Write a compound inequality representing the possible number of calories he could burn daily.","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":3,"Answer":"2000<=x<=2500","Source":"Beginning Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[c - 2000 >= 0, c - 2500 <= 0 , c , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"The temperature in a greenhouse must be kept between 60 and 80 Fahrenheit Degree for optimal plant growth. The temperature control system is set up so that the temperature can fluctuate by up to 5 degree. Write a compound inequality that represents the acceptable range of temperatures for the greenhouse.","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":3,"Answer":"55<=t<=85","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[t - 55 >= 0, t - 85 <= 0 , t , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"The sum of four time a number and eight is between zero and twelve","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":3,"Answer":"-2<=x<=1","Source":"Beginning Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[4*n + 8 - 0 >= 0, 4*n + 8 - 12 <= 0 , n , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"The total of three times a number and fifteen is between six and twenty-seven.","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":3,"Answer":"-3<=x<=4","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[3*n + 15 - 6 >= 0, 3*n + 15 - 27 <= 0 , n , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"The difference between twice a number and five is at least -3 but no more than 9.","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":3,"Answer":"1<=x<=7","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[2*n - 5 - (-3) >= 0, 2*n - 5 - 9 <= 0 , n , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"If a number is multiplied by 4 and then 8 is added to the result, the sum falls between 0 and 12. Find the possible range of the number.","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":3,"Answer":"-2<=n<=1","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[4*n + 8 - 0 >= 0, 4*n + 8 - 12 <= 0 , n , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"The difference between twice a number and five is less than or equal to seven, but greater than or equal to negative three.","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":3,"Answer":"1<=x<=6","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[2*n - 5 - (-3) >= 0, 2*n - 5 - 7 <= 0 , n , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"A company wants to hire a part-time employee and is willing to pay an hourly wage between $15 and $20, inclusive. The employee is expected to work at least 20 hours but no more than 30 hours per week. Write a compound inequality representing the possible weekly earnings of the part-time employee.","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":5,"Answer":null,"Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[15*20 - e <= 0, 20*30 - e >= 0 , e , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"A rectangle has a length of  7 inches. Find all possible widths if the area is to be at least  14 square inches and at most  28 square inches.","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":4,"Answer":"2 <= x <= 4","Source":"Beginning Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[7*x >= 14, 7*x <= 28, x, solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"The perimeter of a square must be between  40 feet and  200 feet. Find the length of all possible sides that satisfy this condition.","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":4,"Answer":"10 <= x <= 50 ","Source":"Beginning Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[4*s - 40 >= 0, 4*s - 200 <= 0 , s , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Anna is thinking of a number. If you subtract five from three times her number, the result is between negative two and ten. What are the possible values of Anna's number?","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":4,"Answer":"1<=x<=5","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[3*a - 5 - (-2) >= 0, 3*a - 5 - 10 <= 0 , a , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"A restaurant needs to purchase new tables that seat between 4 and 8 people each. If the restaurant wants to have enough seating for at least 80 people but no more than 200 people, what is the range for the number of tables they should purchase?","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":4,"Answer":null,"Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[4*t - 80 >= 0, 8*t - 200 <= 0 , t , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"A teacher is organizing a field trip for her students. She wants to divide the students into groups, with each group containing the same number of students. If the number of students in each group is seven, and the total number of students is between 42 and 56, what is the possible range of groups the teacher can create?","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":4,"Answer":"6<=x<=8","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[7*g - 42 >= 0, 7*g - 56 <= 0 , g , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"About 20% of the time you sleep is spent in rapid eye movement (REM) sleep,which is associated with dreaming.If an adult sleeps 7 to 8 hours,how much time is spent in REM sleep","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":4,"Answer":"1.4<=x<=1.6","Source":"Beginning Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[r - 1.4 >= 0, r - 1.6 <= 0 , r , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"A store is offering a $30 mail in rebate on all color printers.Luis is looking at different color printer that range in price from $175 to $260.How much can he expect to spend after the rebate","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":5,"Answer":"145<=x<=230","Source":"Beginning Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[p + 30 - 175 >= 0, p + 30 - 260 <= 0 , p , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"A bookstore offers a discount on all books priced between $15 and $50. The discount ranges from 15% to 25% off the original price, depending on the book's category. Emily wants to buy a book that costs $30 before the discount. What is the possible range of prices she can expect to pay after the discount?","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":5,"Answer":"22.5<=x<=25.5","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[30*0.75 - b <= 0, 30*0.85 - b >= 0 , b , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"A company is planning to rent a bus for a corporate event. The bus rental company charges a flat fee of $200 for the first 20 miles and an additional $5 per mile for any distance beyond that. The company wants to keep the total cost of the bus rental between $500 and $800. Additionally, they want to ensure that the total distance traveled is at least 50 miles but not more than 100 miles. What is the possible range of miles the company can travel while meeting both the cost and distance requirements?","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":5,"Answer":"80<=d<=100","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[200 + 5*(d - 20) - 500 >= 0, 200 + 5*(d - 20) - 800 <= 0, d -50 >= 0, d - 100 <= 0 , d , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Due to the drought in California, many communities now have tiered water rates. There are different rates for Conservation Usage, Normal Usage and Excessive Usage. The usage is measured in the number of hundred cubic feet (hcf) the property owner uses. During the summer, a property owner will pay $24.72 plus $1.32 per hcf for Conservation Usage. The bill for Conservation Usage would be between or equal to $31.32 and $51.12. How many hcf can the owner use if she wants her usage to stay in the conservation range?","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":5,"Answer":"5<=x<=20","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[24.72 + 1.32*h - 31.32 >= 0, 24.72 + 1.32*h - 51.12 <= 0 , h , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"A local energy company has introduced a new billing system to encourage energy conservation. The system has three tiers: Eco-Friendly Usage, Standard Usage, and High Usage. The usage is measured in kilowatt-hours (kWh). During the summer months, a customer will pay a base fee of $15.50 plus $0.12 per kWh for Eco-Friendly Usage. The bill for Eco-Friendly Usage would be between or equal to $21.50 and $39.50. How many kWh can the customer use if they want their usage to stay in the Eco-Friendly range?","Type":"Compound Inequalities","Level":5,"Answer":"50<=x<=200","Source":null,"Symbolic Form":"[[15.50 + 0.12*u - 21.50 >= 0, 15.50 + 0.12*u - 39.50 <= 0 , u , solve]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
